foxwoods.com 2015-05-29

# Foxwoods Resort Casino

Foxwoods Resort Casino ("Foxwoods", "us" or "we") respects the privacy of all visitors to our Web site. We maintain this site to market and promote the many services and amenities offered by Foxwoods. In order to assist us in better serving our customers, we may collect certain anonymous information automatically, and may require certain personal information, including financial information, if you are making reservations or purchases or requesting information from us through this Web site. This Privacy Statement outlines the type of information that Foxwoods may collect and the manner in which such information will be used. All efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy of the information provided herein, however Foxwoods makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy of the information supplied herein. 

Foxwoods is a wholly-owned instrumentality of the Mashantucket Pequot Tribal Nation.

 **Anonymous Information Automatically Collected**  
We may collect and use certain information about your use of this Web site that does not personally identify you. This information includes your IP address and other information gathered through the use of "cookies". Cookies enable us to gather anonymous click-stream information, such as pages viewed, the date and time the site was entered, the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This anonymous information does not personally identify you, and is gathered to help us develop generalized customer profiles to better serve our customers.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most browsers allow users to accept or reject cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services that we offer on our Web site.

 **Personal Information Collected  
** You may be required to supply personal information such as your name, address, telephone number and/or email address in order to receive certain information, participate in promotions, make reservations or place orders. A personal identification number provided by Foxwoods may be required to access certain personal information. By providing personal information, you agree to be placed on marketing lists and may receive promotional materials from Foxwoods from time to time.

Your personal information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your personal information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped Web browser. Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by Foxwoods employees on a "need to know" basis. In order to ensure that all of your personal information is correct and up to date, you will be able to update your personal information. While we strive to protect your personal information, Foxwoods cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

 **Age Policy  
** Foxwoods Resort Casino has no intention of collecting any personal information (such as name, address, telephone number or email address) from individuals under 21 years of age. Any offers, promotions or contests we conduct are not open to persons younger than 21 years of age. We reserve the right to verify age at any time for any reason and may reject a person who does not have valid age identification as requested by Foxwoods. If a child has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the email address or phone number listed at the bottom of this Privacy Statement to identify the information that must be removed.

 **Sharing Information  
** The personal information you provide may be shared with other businesses owned or managed by the Mashantucket Pequot Tribe. These entities include The Spa at Norwich Inn, the Mashantucket Pequot Museum & Research Center and PRxN. We do not anticipate that your personal information will be shared or divulged to any non-affiliated third parties by us, provided such disclosure may be necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authorities, including but not limited to authorities which regulate gaming activities; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Foxwoods.

This Web site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Changes to Privacy Statement  
** We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Statement simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Web site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web site.

 **Copyright**  
All contents of this Web site are: Copyright © 2001-2014 Foxwoods Resort Casino, Route 2, Mashantucket, Connecticut, 06338. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
